lscconnect.com 2019-06-28

# Privacy Policy | LSC

### We Are

LSC Ltd, Unit 5, Kinsale Commercial Park, Kinsale, Co. Cork. We are a project resourcing company, placing specialist consultants on business critical projects with in the pharmaceutical, medical device and biotechnology industry in Ireland and Europe.

### Our Website

LSC has designed its website to provide information to visitors about our business and services. At times we will collect information about your visit and combine this with other information to understand how all visitors use our site. At other times we will collect personal information about you, for example your email address and Curriculum Vitae (“CV”) details. This policy explains how we use these types of data.

### Online Visitors (Aggregated Information)

Gathering information and statistics on all of our visitors to our website enables us to understand what content visitors are consuming and what they are most interested in on the sites. This data is analysed and used to improve our website and deliver a better service to our visitors. We collect domain names and IP addresses of our visitors’ Internet Service Provider, but no personally identifiable information is revealed during this process.

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a token that a server gives to your browser when you access an Internet website. Cookies are capable of storing many types of data. Cookies help us provide additional functionality to the site or to help us analyse site usage more accurately. In all cases in which cookies are used, the cookie will not collect personally identifiable information except with your explicit permission.

### Other Websites

We may provide links to third party Internet sites and clicking on these links may take you to other websites. LSC is not responsible for the privacy policies of these sites and visitors will need to refer to them specifically.

### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

LSC may invite you to submit personal information about you through, for example, the “Submit CV” page on the website. The information you provide us will normally include, name, address, email address, phone number and employment history.

This information is used by us to:

  * provide our recruitment services to you, whether you are a client, candidate or a user of our website;
  * enable you to submit your CV generally to apply for specific jobs;
  * provide information on suitable job opportunities to people who register with us, to match your profile with suitable job vacancies and to assist us in finding a position that is most suitable for you.
  * answer your enquiry;
  * provide other services related to or supplementary to the above; market related products and services directly to you to your professional or business email address.
  * after contacting you and with your permission we might send your personal information to clients in order to apply for jobs;
  * send relevant industry news directly to your personal email address.
  * if we need to process special category/sensitive data about you, we will first seek your consent.

Within the scope of the purposes outlined above, we may outsource the processing of collected personal information to outside contractors/third parties. If we do so, we will take contractual measures to ensure that they process your data in a manner consistent with this Policy. For those companies who operate in countries outside the EU, which may not offer a level of data protection equivalent to the high standards that exist in Europe, we take contractual steps to ensure that the same high standards are upheld.

### Other Sources of Data

We may also process information about you where it is available from public sources. For example, if you have a professional profile online we may combine that type of information with the information you provide directly to us.

### Curriculum Vitae (“CV”)

By sending us your CV you are indicating you have read and understand our privacy policy and acknowledge that LSC will process your personal details in the manner described above.

### Job and Industry News

Once you have sent us your CV we will keep in touch by email and phone to let you know about jobs, industry news and events. Should you decide you’d prefer not to receive these updates, please contact us by email at [data@lsc.ie](mailto:data@lsc.ie) to unsubscribe.

### Subject Access Request

You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold for you on our systems. In order to receive this information, you can email us at [data@lsc.ie](mailto:data@lsc.ie) and we will respond within 1 month. We will need verification of your identity to process this request.

### Updating your Information

You have the right to correct any inaccuracies in your information. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us at [data@lsc.ie](mailto:data@lsc.ie) and we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect or incomplete.

### Deletion of Data

You have the right to erasure. This is also known as ‘the right to be forgotten’ and, in simple terms, enables you to request the deletion or removal of your information where there’s no compelling reason for us to keep using it. This is not a general right to erasure; there are exceptions. Should you wish to have the data we hold on you deleted, please inform us in writing at [data@lsc.ie](mailto:data@lsc.ie)

### Changes to Our Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time and continued use of the site or our services after changes are made will constitute your acceptance of the revised policy.

### Contact Us

If you have any queries on our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at [data@lsc.ie](mailto:data@lsc.ie) or in writing to:

LSC, Unit 5, Kinsale Commercial Park, Kinsale, Co. Cork.
